Till which class you are I had promised you
that I will share accordingly
which kami doh line is offering
so for those who are watching the kami doh line for you then this
video will be very useful for them
and you will get to
know the difference in all the maternity plans and
you will also know which one to choose all the
thinking in starting I have two daughters average bun
friends my name is Prince Chiku and
I am with you every inch and I have been associated with MS Word
Global for the last six years
and similarly I
bring you this video in which I will
talk about your praise and I will
focus on that simplified and how to become
that your company's tagline is
creating awareness of his mobile phone to do with different matter
of kami available in
India so in this the plan which I am going to compare is
ICICI Lombard
Health Advantage Nibhao Premium Plan
Gold Nibhao Film Airplane Plan No 4
Help Comprehensive's recent years were
flying  Jatt Day So if I make this reference comeback
then I will see
what coverage is there in quality and
apart from maternity, massage if you want a health insurance layer
top that one plan I will play you everything in
my maternity coverage if you
want it to work for health insurance as well then
what are the health insurance plans
available and what all do you
need to know so I had a
pin here in this number detail Vantage I am
comparing Prime Royala Tips hair oil
and Max Bupa's premier plan is
Gold Max Bupa Print Planet
Platinum weight also now I will press this also
you will know in the video
why I am making a comeback some such benefits
size that are not available in Gold I am adding this
year's comprehensive plan is one line and
this pipeline join today so the white
heads and white present planets Amazon
today cup and
what is the basic eligibility criteria for first attack from this
Mumtaz Mahal in three years maximum
entry 16594 latest ninth day settings
maximum  If the dependent age is saved he
can continue in college he has a
minimum balance of 2500 in good platinum plan
which gives you maximum entry this juice
minimum entry get
your new born baby covered in the policy
automatically their channel is thirty
years which means six years in quality of the system
resident can continue sadhu
and comprehensive minimum infinity in
maximum entries such five and minimum
wages for child line yes and maximum
entry will be 825 and in different size and
plan the joint minimum is 2018 maximum
entry is 35 and maximum different size
bed is 24 years room rent if we talk about this then
such people can also stay in flood dozens of room rent shopping
which can buy rings paper
printer gold up to someeshwar clothes
you can also take but of education
but cannot buy sweets
in Microsoft world platinum you
cannot stay including needle and year
comprehensive insurance in diet plan
in both single private is serum  The
rest, before comparing the differences, let's
focus on the button. So first of all, we are
taking this line, so
what will you get in Mitthu Mitthu, Nick line, some
specific lines have come, their detailed videos are
available on my channel, like you will get it for
Body Advantage, you will get
this line for Max Bupa, so you
should see it in detail, there you can do it,
I will cover the points of
difference, if we talk on the basis of comparison,
you will do those points, so the
maternity cover which is Aslam Health Advantage,
after that there is an option to take this news,
for that you will have to pay three years of upfront
premium, if you want
early maternity cover, that means you
want to work early with your delivery, then
after that you can take this benefit,
but you will have to pay three years of upfront
premium in it, Max Bupa Health
Prem Yudh Plants Golden Partner,
both have a waiting period of 24th March,
after that Thomas we can autotune,
3G in all school principals also  Its
waiting list is clear in the phone, so let's break it down, there is a
waiting ticket for it and simply
you have to take the premium of the rear or the front, but it was said that
if we talk about constipation, then
such people in Advantage, Temple Staff, Chilli
Powder, Maximum Oil, so whatever you understand about the
policy, its time person, fatigue,
can take airplane, Max Bupa Health
Premium has
positive limit at different times in different houses, if you take the plan of Felt, then I am
talking about it strongly, then you will
take an explanation, then there is antigen MS Word, if
we take the premium plan of Maximum, then it is
less than 108 from the other side,
you can take maximum ₹2 there, but a complaint
and thing, and here the Worldwide tree is
also residing in Vasant Canada, if you want to get your
delivery done outside India, then that
option is available, but only after two years
and except for the US, you
can scan for your delivery anywhere,
in the year comprehensive you get the possession of holidays,
introduction of soil which you can play the
most forceful game in the line  If we play cards for newborn baby
Amresh, then for Human Devi, we will
talk about such people in half an hour. The
word for baby is sewing or you have taken a policy from there,
you will have to pay approximately 19th class with knowledge, so the
fabric of New Mandi is the same as the
riders, you will get different riders for your
maternity, when will we explain why we are going to
talk against the previous Anshu,
your newborn baby's tree will be 1
minute, because the choice of the Mutton ATM you are taking,
you will get Dubai coverage from this, with this, you will get
premier gold plated number in the match in Iron Wrestler Test, till
next year annual, suppose you
took the policy today and after completing 2 years in mid term,
you deliver in June,
now if I read the policy and from now on,
newborn baby coverage will automatically be included
in the policy, after 9120, if you do
not get time, then when you renew your policy on next renewal, then till
next renewal,
newborn baby coverage remains from the company and
their express up to sound less.  It
is a trap, in comprehensive, you will have to pay
diesel premium to IDBI and
close Muslim only schedule health advantage
like birthday
or premium, you have to request
definition on one side that
if you in Bigg Boss first year but this first year second
year mainly definition
is wrong its cost is high for children
so that they can
take definition poetry here with Congress so you can
add it in your body here you will
invest in other plants such option in Salman
gets a mix of choice
maximum your tent house but practice
attached also prominent you can take
vaccination in Max Bupa premium
I bathed a lot in the market now I am not used to
lemon saying Sunil Babu granddaughters
in gold and platinum both have a
special aspect stitch less according to that you have a
question because cost will be given
on platinum tears of a child will become mission repeat
for 12 years friends of this country if you are
part of Lucknow policy then give this only
media platinum this in any other policy
you will get  You will not get Taj Mahal
in comprehensive coverage. The first year definition
is birthday. Maximum phase is that if he does not join then
this is balance of vitality but
all teachers. I will write a lot of maternity to
add rider. You will have to choose from these
numbers from side to side.
Mode on why illegal connection is
maximum. If I take only modernity option then
emojis will automatically come. SIM boss
health and time care. Daily intercourse is a
plan of peas soil only. Gurjar name shows that
want to day, so maternity was to be fed
but a specific plan is automatically
covered. You will see its result. And
one more thing is required in festivals, after this we
cannot take maternity benefit. This
cannot be done. And I would like to tell you one more thing,
in the added advantage, you have a serious
problem given in front and suppose you do not have any
problem, then there is no problem of maternity benefit. The
company will wave the premium of female asthma licorice benefit. Let us take you to the
rest of the benefits.
We have talked about collecting apart from of clans
and I have got happiness so this will
talk about hospitalization, people
in Advantage have 1601 ingredients Max
Bupa Premier Golden Plot number nine
three days this is adversely in the 90s ago with
a pen the death boxer work
comprehensive message pendrive desk a
pune in desperate stage to senses but will
talk about no claim bonus, its length
advantage body uses guaranteed why
minute bonus so guaranteed means that
once you are given the bonus it will continue
they will not withdraw from you
attack is not Muslim cloth so
lets you get 20% no
claim bonus of polytechnic Amit Vikram style if you
take next9 then the bonus of Rs 2 lakh that I have
given you - we will not do it but we will
transfer it to you otherwise it will remain there so it
means that the
policy you have taken for UK return is 20% no claim
You get a bonus and if your Play
Services are completed, if the Glass
policy is included then you will be robbed of a maximum of 20x, it is a
problem, so this
Rs. 10 Molly Molly, if you mix it
in Max Bupa Premium line,
then use the loyalty addition here, it
came out in the morning, this is a loyalty bonus that you were continuing with them,
Almighty Hus has nothing to do
with taking risk, so the
sent of is always on time, mother meeting 2012, 10 lakh
policy will go up to 20 lakh, 1
crore policy will mature on 2 crore
and - it will not come, then any
positive Vaseline, ask us, it is not robbed, we will
talk about it in Sagar Comprehensive Plan, there
is a no claim bonus of up
to a maximum of 100 percent, you can click
and it will come the next day, so - it may also happen, hair
oil, this is available,
you can take the teacher but additional result of no claim bonus, that
means if you have taken a policy and you have taken an
addition rider  No claim
bonus of this is called no claim bonus, if
you have taken a rider then what will happen in it, if
your renewal comes after next year
then Someshwar was hundred percent, you will give it to everyone,
this is a silent policy, you have
not taken no claim bonus for some time,
next year we have
not made it effective, no one else believes in this, then
for that you have been given ₹5 additional bonus,
Mike Hooper is available in Premier Golden Platinum
International Travel Insurance,
which is not available in any other plan, so
if you travel a lot then if you
take this line then you do
not need to take any questions, so
whatever is there related to festivals, we
include it in it, we talk about it, confidence
event, in every policy you get complimentary -
let's meet, in saver mode one test,
point five percent of the reviewer can get a maximum of
₹10 cut off, so you can get Max
Super Hands Free installed at 275 in Gold
and Desires and
Superhit in Premier Platinum, your tent
house is installed at notice  If you click on it, then you
can change your mind completely and in such moments, you
can do it one by one after the completion of one month,
you can add your business matter Vyas policy after one month, if there is a
problem in March, you can definitely click on it,
along with this,
you will get Anil Tas in the comprehensive plan and the maximum
limit is ₹2000 and you can change it only on free mode,
next if you change your policy
then you can limit
that if the alarm is not available then
please talk about it, it will
manifest and it happens that now your shopping with
friends or someone else, then the company
always inspects your purse, you will
understand that all the plants have
power, then ICC is long, don't, it will be
recorded once and aliens
for anything we can do any person and
that Mike Hooper in premium, in platinum, in
round, in both, you can take 108, in
orange color as well as in comprehensive, answers
on NH-91, medical benefit  It is not available, if we
talk about treatment then they
take 500 policies and
sleep as a birthday gift of treatment which because of the judgment of science
you do
not need D84 hospitalization, you go during the day and get the
surgery done and come home, if the treatment comes to
your home, friends here, how long will we
talk about AYUSH coverage, AYUSH
is Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha, Homeopathic
hospitalization, its word is a
moment, there is a comment in the middle, Moscow
premium plan, gold and platinum back cover,
cover up to 100 waste oil and
in Star Health Insurance, there is Kabaddi, two fifty thousand rupees, there is
no comment in clear sharp red, we will talk about ambulance, we are
innocent, who is healthy, from this movement, road
ambulance, emergency road imbalance, so its word is
ICC hosted test,
so I will do it in finishing world of
Titan, emergency road
ambulance cover up to emperor, no limit,
Aaj Ka rashifal, if you
go to Noida property, means you are
not taking it in skit, which is not their type,
with CPI(M)  There you will get ₹2000 on
hospitalization, the insurance company will
reverse the change, here there
is news of emergency deep lens, contra voucher platinum,
also emergency air ambulance, you have a
comment on that too, in ICC Awards and Honors
also there is news of road ambulance in the car,
this ambulance is also news, this is the
button of road boys in the line, if we talk about thousand rupees for play's
OPD pencil, then speed is
a pan sentence, what is the inches length advantage, it is
also top in Max Bupa Premier Platinum
Gold, Saharan speed
is a senses but this is not news in alarm, in the
same way there is some limit,
see that this mode setting is on the spot,
now let's talk about some questions,
accuracy of maternity,
waiting period of mutton, so we see
what is different in this last, if from side to
Mumtaz Mahal, it is ninth in an hour, that the
alarm which I have given on one side and maximum in
premium golden platinum both
and 10 year comprehensive plan  In this also we will talk about two
years
specifications, for those who have
just done it, their activation waiting
period itself, but hey don't touch me, it is two
years, you can reduce it by
taking extra cream, in Max Bupa
Health Premium Golden Time both have
specific public waiting period and on
star cost we submit to your taste and
festival also two years kids, if we talk about its best
interior then your AC
is printed in the cover, two years, you can
increase it by three or four years, that
option is available, you can increase it, then
its punishment will be reduced a bit, in both Max
Bupa Premium Plan and Golden Partner there is
two years,
in this comprehensive plan it is of course, if we
talk about your medical checkup, then
in such body the policy medical checkup is
not being done right now, meaning the tests which are done before taking the policy are being done, the same
tests are being done,
in Max Bupa Health Premium
Good Time also in both the versions, there will be tests of one year
in comprehensive, forest
department and medical condition and clear
sharp lines, above that, so
basically you  Even the PM has its policy, the
guidelines and roles of medical checkup,
they keep changing. Exam date, let me
tell you what are the roles of PM.
We have made a policy of 1234 shade, water and maturity in 500 yards.
If
you want maternity cover, then
you will have to take it seriously for half an hour. Same
quotes for Pune
Someshwar options are available in I Serum Health
Advantage Rohit Plan.
You can choose from 6 lakh to 15 lakh options. Max Bupa Premium
Plan is available in Godap. Delast 30
Delast 30 Delast 365 Miyan
Platinum Hostel is available for 2 crore internal and
on Star Health Volume,
from supply fault to stop, there is an option that is
available for problems of only 3 lakh 95 lakh. So our computer is
faulty and like Salman
is for Strauss while walking, Moscow has
taken back the gold medal in the film Mafia Platinum
because including the minimum is 54 crores.  So my
mind is for crores and I have taken comprehensive
plan tax payable year and this alarm in
me because maximum time and faults
are available from both the options will show 315 so
I have taken cream on this day of
their Delhi here also
you can do solar panels for yourself so if you look for
tamarind in John William
from highway it is 3535 12312 whatever is its thing and the
premium on that is definitely reduced trim
including percent GST so it is a
romantic advantage of bringing him IT
forces institute of slow loss talk
if there is a student in Max Super
Premium Plan Gold your premium
is 30000 rupees in Maps Open
Premier Platinum you tax Shravan 10 years
comprehensive coverage cream is 1000
rupees and clear joint series result is
that from Twenty20 for boil pregnant
seniors and share your eyes years
rest of the same is the premium for the year so this was
from my side now I have  500ml computer
network okay so if you look at it with me then the
clear job line does
n't appeal to me a lot you vacation the
smallest white cardamom we maximum and
premium league friendly if your feet will do
such slot advantage and its love there is
not much difference but the
benefits here are quite less complaint is still on between
if you want to take a fast for nine
months for maternity so I don't give any and
give this number
disadvantage according to Bhumija better option
and if you have New York meeting you can keep it
you feel that this is not necessary for maternity you
can take Max Bupa Premium Gold for yourself or you
can see the requirement of Platinum S
then detailed videos are also made
both last step chapters are ours
ask any question you can tell us directly if
you feel anything got done
tell us there have been some experience in
getting sperm donation claim from that company so
share that too with our liver  CFO also,
leave from that too, questions you can connect us,
our phone number email ID is below,
Happy Promise Day, if you have
not subscribed to my channel yet then please
subscribe, my promise is that
you will keep getting information and we will meet soon,
Ajay had brought a face
[Music]
Ajay has got a baby,
Ajay
[Music]